name: 'Present Continuous'
questions:
  -
    question: 'I can''t have lunch now, I''''''''m $.'
    answers:
      - work
      - worked
      - working
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'What $ you eating?'
    answers:
      - do
      - are
      - â€“
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'A: What are you doing here?\nB: I $ for my friend.'
    answers:
      - wait
      - waiting
      - '''m waiting'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I can go shopping with you. I $ today!'
    answers:
      - '''m not work'
      - '''m not working'
      - 'don''t working'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: "A: Excuse me! You $ in my seat.\nB: Sorry!"
    answers:
      - '''re sitting'
      - '''re sit'
      - sit
    correct: 1
  -
    question: "A: $ her homework?\nB: No, she $."
    answers:
      - 'Is Jane do'
      - 'Does Jane doing'
      - 'Is Jane doing'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'She $ to her boifriend on the phone now.'
    answers:
      - talking
      - talks
      - '''s talking'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Look! It $!'
    answers:
      - snows
      - '''s snowing'
      - '''s snows'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: "A: Where $?\nB: To the beach!"
    answers:
      - 'do you going'
      - 'you''re going'
      - 'are you going'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: Where $ in New York?\nB: At a hotel.'
    answers:
      - 'is your sister staying'
      - 'your sister is staying'
      - 'does your sister staying'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'A: What are your children doing?\nB: They $ games.'
    answers:
      - play
      - 'are play'
      - 'are playing'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: What $?\nB: Harry Potter!'
    answers:
      - 'are you reading'
      - 'do you reading'
      - 'you''re reading'
    correct: 1
